<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cinema 21</string>
    <string name="txtusr"><![CDATA[<Username>]]></string>
    <string name="nameSaekano">Saenai Heroine no Sodate-kata fine</string>
    <string name="descSaekano">Tomoya Aki, an otaku, has been obsessed with collecting anime and light novels for years,
        attaching himself to various series with captivating stories and characters.
        Now, he wants to have a chance of providing the same experience for others by creating his own game,
        but unfortunately, Tomoya cannot do this task by himself.
        He successfully recruits childhood friend Eriri Spencer Sawamura to illustrate and literary elitist
        Utaha Kasumigaoka to write the script for his visual novel, while he directs. Super-group now in hand,
        Tomoya only needs an inspiration to base his project on, and luckily meets the beautiful, docile Megumi Katou,
        who he then models his main character after.

        Using what knowledge he has, Tomoya creates a new doujin circle with hopes to touch the hearts of those who play their game.
        What he does not realize, is that to invoke these emotions, the creators have had to experience the same feelings in
        their own lives.
</string>
    <string name="namePikachu">Pokémon Detective Pikachu</string>
    <string name="descPikachu">A young man joins forces with Detective Pikachu to unravel the mystery behind his father`s disappearance.
        Chasing clues through the streets of Ryme City, the dynamic duo soon discover a devious plot
        that poses a threat to the Pokémon universe.</string>
    <string name="nameSeishun">Seishun Buta Yarou wa Bunny Girl Senpai no Yume wo Minai</string>
    <string name="descSeishun">The rare and inexplicable Puberty Syndrome is thought of as a myth.
        It is a rare disease which only affects teenagers, and its symptoms are so supernatural that hardly anyone recognizes it
        as a legitimate occurrence. However, high school student Sakuta Azusagawa knows from personal experience that it is very
        much real, and happens to be quite prevalent in his school.

        Mai Sakurajima is a third-year high school student who gained fame in her youth as a child actress,
        but recently halted her promising career for reasons unknown to the public. With an air of unapproachability,
        she is well known throughout the school, but none dare interact with her—that is until Sakuta sees her wandering
        the library in a bunny girl costume. Despite the getup, no one seems to notice her, and after confronting her, he
        realizes that she is another victim of Puberty Syndrome. As Sakuta tries to help Mai through her predicament, his
        actions bring him into contact with more girls afflicted with the elusive disease.</string>


    <string name="navigation_open">
    Open
    </string>
    <string name="navigation_close">
        Close

    </string>
</resources>
